sousa kanashimi wo yasashisa ni jibun rashisa wo chikara ni
turn your sadness into kindness, your uniqueness into strength
mayoinagarademo ii arukidashite
even if you get lost, let's start walking
mou ikkai
one more time
dareka no kitai ni zutto kotae
are you really happy
homerarerunoga suki nano desuka
when you're always meeting to someone's expectations?
naritai jibun wo surikaetemo
even if you change to who you really wanna be
egao wa itsudemo suteki desuka
will you always have a great smile?
hajimaridake yume mite okiru
dreaming of only the beginning, I wake up
sono saki nara itsuka jibun no ude de
and someday, I'll live on my own.
souda daiji na mono wa itsumo katachi no nai mono dake
yes, precious things are never in shape
te ni iretemo nakushitemo kizukanumama
you never know what it is when you get it or lose it
sousa kanashimi wo yasashisa ni jibun rashisa wo chikara ni
turn your sadness into kindness, your uniqueness into strength
mayoinagarademo ii arukidashite
even if you get lost, let's start walking
mou ikkai
one more time
His opponent is that Neji, huh...?
The Final Round is altogether different
than the preliminaries...
After all Naruto may not be able to...
Entertain me a little Naruto-kun.
I've got a tough job waiting
for me now so...
No Blind
Spot!
The Other
Absolute Defense
Damn it. I can't catch him at all.
I told you I'm not
such a fool didn't I?
I already know...
which one is the real one.
Oh.
That is the body
that has the least attacks
due to its fear of having
Chakra Points attacked.
The more you attack
the more that one body
becomes clearly evident.
You're the real one.
Naruto-kun...
This is as far as it goes.
I said it was pointless.
Don't let him beat you Naruto-kun.
I've been telling you not
to frivolously assume things.
What?
It can't be.
All right! Go Naruto!
Naruto-kun...!
He foiled my idea and purposely
and drew one of his clones back?
I've been striking from the beginning
prepared for an honorable death!
I did it.
That's...
W-What was that?
Did you think you'd won?
Why?
Naruto's punch should've hit.
That...
Rotation...
That's Neji's defense.
You punk.
Don't make a fool of me.
The largest range of vision of
Neji's Byakugan is nearly 360 degrees.
And he detects all of his opponent's
attacks with the Byakugan.
His defense technique
the 8 Trigrams Palms Rotation
will begin from here.
The moment he's attacked
he discharges a large amount of Chakra
from the Chakra holes in the body
blocks the enemy's attack with that Chakra
moves his own body in a circular motion
dodges and repels.
Essentially it's difficult to control
the Chakra discharged from Chakra holes...
To the extent that even Jonin utilize
the discharge from a part of the body
like the hands and feet
in techniques.
But Neji who has mastered
Gentle Fist discharges Chakra
from his entire body and
shuts out physical attacks
just with that discharge power.
In other words
that's one more absolute defense
that has more power
than that Gaara's Sand Shield.
T-That's father's...
The Rotation is a secret Art passed down
from generation to generation
only to the Hyuga head family
in other words the Hyuga clan.
He created that on his own...?
He's quite the guy...
To think he'd come this far.
It's much too soon to be surprised.
Neji's true power is still to come.
Damn it.
This is the end.
You're within the area of my 8 Trigrams.
Gentle Fist Art.
8 Trigrams 64 Palms.
It can't be.
That pose.
8 Tetragrams...
...2 Palms!
4 Palms.
8 Palms.
16 Palms.
32 Palms.
64 Palms!
The branch family exceeds
the head family?
It's over.
Truly a terrifying talent.
To think the power of the
Hyuga Kekkei Genkai
would be passed on so strongly
to a child of the branch family
who would never be able
to be an heir.
Hizashi... You should have
succeeded the Hyuga family.
I pressed the 64 Chakra Points
all over your body...
You can't even stand.
D-Damn it.
Are you frustrated?
Kneeling down before power
that can't be changed
and knowing your powerlessness.
Your dreams will come true
if you just work hard.
That's just an illusion.
Hey, Hinata. Are you okay?
Oh man. I knew it.
Naruto.
Bushy brow...
Hinata.
D-Damn it.
Oh.
Naruto.
He... No way.
I told you didn't I...?
I don't know when to give up.
No way.
Hey, you're bleeding.
What's wrong?
You've still got damage
from the match.
Hinata... Hang in there.
I'll take a look at her.
Who're you?
I'm not suspicious or anything.
Stop already...
It'll be the same even if
you fight more than this.
I don't have a grudge particularly
against you.
S-Shut up...
Even if you say so
I have something against you.
What are you talking about?
Why...? Here you're this strong...
Why did you with a look like
you've seen through it all
go after Hinata mentally
who was trying so hard?
It has nothing to do with you.
Mocking Hinata selfishly labeling
her a failure as you please.
Head family branch family...
I don't know what happened to you.
But I won't forgive the jerk who'd
call another person a failure.
Hey you.
It's okay. I'm a doctor.
Okay... Fine.
If you insist I'll tell you about
the Hyuga's destiny of hatred.
In the Hyuga head family
there's a secret Ninjutsu
that's been passed on
from generation to generation.
That is the Curse Mark Arts.
Curse Mark Arts?
The Curse Mark represents
a bird in a cage...
and it's a mark of those who are
bound to a destiny they can't escape.
W-What's...
...t-that mark?
One day when I was four years old
this accursed mark was inscribed
on my forehead with the Curse Mark Arts.
A large ceremony was held in
the Village Hidden in Leaves on that day.
It was also the day when the
head Ninja of the Land of Lightning
the land that the Leaf had
fought with for many years
came for the conclusion
of the allied treaty.
However there was one clan...
who didn't attend the ceremony
that was attended
by everybody else
from Leaf Jonin to Genin.
It was the Hyuga clan...
And it's because that day
was the day of hope
when the head family heir
was to turn three.
Hinata-sama's third birthday!
My father Hyuga Hizashi
and Hinata-sama's father who's over there
Hyuga Hiashi-sama were twin brothers.
However Hinata-sama's father
Hiashi-sama
is the eldest son of the head family
born into this world first.
And my father who was the second son
is a member of the branch family.
So Hinata-sama is already three...
Congratulations.
Thank you.
She's a cute girl isn't she father?
What's wrong, father?
Oh, it's nothing.
Then...
I'll be taking Neji under my care Hizashi.
Yes.
When the head family heir grew
and became three years old
I had the Curse Mark imprinted on me
and I became the bird in the cage.
And became the Hyuga branch family.
Why's it necessary to do
something like that?
Why separate into a head family
and a branch family?
What does that weird mark mean?
This mark on my forehead
isn't just a decoration.
The pull of your legs is weak.
Yes.
Listen Neji.
You will live to protect Hinata-sama
of the head family
as well as the Hyuga power.
Yes, father.
Murderous Intent.
My head.
Father.
What's wrong father?
Go home.
I'll forgive the fool today only.
You're not to forget your destiny.
This Curse Mark is the absolute fear
called death so to speak...
that was given to the branch family
by the head family.
The Secret Sign that the
head family members form easily
destroys the cerebral nerves
of those in the branch family.
Of course killing is easy.
And this mark only goes away
at time of death.
Sealing away the power
of the Byakugan.
The Hyuga family is the clan that possesses
the most distinctive Kekkei Genkai.
There's no end to those who
target the secret of that distinctive power.
In other words this Curse Mark
keeps the branch family alive
only to protect the head family
and does not allow disobedience.
And it's an effective system created
to defend for eternity
the Kekkei Genkai called Byakugan.
And then that incident occurred.
My father was killed by
the head family.
One night Hinata-sama was
snatched up by someone.
At that time Hiashi-sama immediately
rushed off and killed the abductor.
Who do you think that person was...
who was in the shadows
and also wearing a mask?
It was the head Shinobi of
the Land of Lightning
who had just completed
the allied treaty.
It was clear that he came targeting
the secret of Byakugan from the start.
However the Land of Lightning
exploited the killing of their own Shinobi
due to a botched plan...
and set an outrageous condition in
violation of the treaty with the Hidden Leaf.
Naturally things got worse and worse
and there was almost a war
between the Leaf and the Lightning.
However, the Leaf who
wanted to avoid war
made a deal with the Lightning.
A deal?
The Lightning demand was
the body of the Hyuga head family
who possesses Byakugan
the Kekkei Genkai...
In other words
the body of Hiashi-sama.
And the Leaf accepted the condition.
What? But father...
And war was safely avoided.
Thanks to my father who was killed
as a body double of Hyuga Hiashi
to protect the head family!
Other than dying there's no other way
to escape this accursed Curse Mark.
Even though they were twins
with nearly equal power
their destinies were already set by
who was born first and born later.
And then this match...
Your destiny was decided at the point
when I became your opponent.
ONE JAMPU ichiban SURAMU DANKU kamasu TAISON
One! first, Tyson jumps and slam-dunks
TWO are mo kore mo dosoku de HAGU KISSU I LOVE YOU
Two! he kisses and hugs everyone randomly and says "I love you"
THREE YOGA wo kiwamemasu KAREE kirai masara san
Three! Masala masters yoga but hates curry
FOUR hetare tougyuushi SANCHESU OREI
Four! Sanchez is a lousy bullfighter, olay!
sekaijuu hora waratteru sora miagete saa tachiagatte
all over the world, the sky's smiling, so look up and smile too
OH YEAH OH YEAH OH YEAH
Oh yeah! Oh yeah! Oh yeah!
FIGHT FIGHT FIGHT
Fight! Fight! Fight!
ONE kokuen bori ni bottou bodi ma haattaya san mo
One! Bodimahattaya devotes his time for digging black ships
TWO PEKIN DAKKU waiyaa AKUSHON chari de isogu CHEN RII
Two! peking Duck, action scene, Chen Lee speeds around on his bike
THREE MY KOTEKA daiji ni migakiageru POPO san
Three! Popo loves to polish his coteka
FOUR ote wo haishaku JAPANIIZU PIIPOO
Four! japanese people, now lend me your hand!
sekaijuu hora waratteru sora miagete saa tachiagatte
all over the world, the sky's smiling, so look up and smile too
OH YEAH OH YEAH OH YEAH
Oh yeah! Oh yeah! Oh yeah!
FIGHT FIGHT FIGHT
Fight! Fight! Fight!
sekaijuu hora kawatteku minna ganbatte so tachiagatte
all over the world, the sky's smiling, so look up and smile too
OH YEAH OH YEAH OH YEAH
Oh yeah! Oh yeah! Oh yeah!
FIGHT FIGHT FIGHT
Fight! Fight! Fight!
Are all my Chakra Points
really closed?
Damn. I cannot feel any Chakra
remaining in my body at all...
just like when I used up all my Chakra
in my training with the Pervy Sage.
Wait. I got it. Just watch me!
I will squeeze out
my Chakra no matter what!
Next time
"The Dropout's Hidden Power!"